<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>RunAndGun</name>
	<author>Roolo</author>
	<supportedVersions>
			<li>1.0</li>
			<li>1.1</li>
	</supportedVersions>
   <packageId>roolo.RunAndGun</packageId>
   
	<modDependencies>
      <li>
        <packageId>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</packageId>
        <displayName>HugsLib</displayName>
        <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=818773962</steamWorkshopUrl>
      </li>  
    </modDependencies>

	<loadAfter>
	  <li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<description> Your colonists can never be a true Rambo if they cannot gun while they are running. Therefore, this mod adds a mode that, when enabled, allows drafted colonists to shoot 
while moving at the cost of an accuracy and movement penalty.These penalties can be modified in the mod settings of this mod. 
Some things to take into account: 
- Fire at will should be enabled. Firing manually will cause the pawn to stop running. 
- RunAndGun mode can only be enabled when the pawn is drafted, and is carrying a ranged weapon in its hands. 
- The movement penalty is only applied at the moment the pawn is actually shooting or cooling down after shooting. So don't bother disabling RunAndGun every time you just want your pawn to walk somewhere. 

&lt;color=orange&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dependencies &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;

This mod depends on Hugslib, so make sure that mod loads before this mod does.

&lt;color=orange&gt;&lt;b&gt;Compatibility &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;

This mod should be compatible with existing saves, and removing the mod from saves shouldn't introduce problems. Moreover, this mod should be compatible with most other mods (including Combat Extended). However, keep in mind that this is hard to test for me by myself, and this is the first release.
Therefore some issues regarding mod compatibility are bound to come up. Most issues that come up should be easy to fix, so please report any problems.  


	</description>	
	
</ModMetaData>
